<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web CV of Masaru NAGASO</title><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Web CV of Masaru NAGASO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mnagaso.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mnagaso.github.io/publications/</guid><description>publication page published M. Nagaso. Study of ultrasound wave propagation in a heterogeneous fluid medium for the monitoring of an operating sodium-based nuclear reactor. Theses, Université d’Aix Marseille, May 2018.
M. Nagaso, D. Komatitsch, J. Moysan, and C. Lhuillier. Numerical simulation of ultrasonic wave propagation in a sodium cooling system in an inhomogeneous temperature field using the spectral-element method. In 19th World Conference on Non-Destructive Testing, Münich, Germany, Jun 2016.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mnagaso.github.io/projects/</guid><description>My former and current projects I/O optimization and designing/developing a workflow toward a full-wave inversion calculation on Exascale HPC machines. This is a project (part of my postdoc works) for code optimization towards a use on Exascale High Performance Computers or supercomputers.
The I/O is one of the significant bottleneck for achieving a scalable computation (the ratio between the number of processors and the computation time is enoughly close to a linear), because the limitation of file I/O bandwidth blocks the other computing processes.</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mnagaso.github.io/resume/</guid><description>Personal date Name: Masaru NAGASO
Address: Marseille, France
github, gitlab, linkedin, researchgate
Language English (fluent) French (intermediate) Japanese (native) Experience 01.june.2019&amp;ndash;31.dec.2021 Postdoctral research assistant
CNRS-LMA, Marseille, France
Co-lead developer of SPECFEM3D for ChEESE project, which is the international project in the domain of geoscience for preparing Exascale HPC founded from [the European Union&amp;rsquo;s Horizon 2020](https://ec.europa.eu/programmes/horizon2020/en}. I/O optimization and designing/developing a workflow toward a full-wave inversion calculation on Exascale HPC machines.</description></item></channel></rss>