<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web CV of Masaru NAGASO</title><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Web CV of Masaru NAGASO</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mnagaso.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mnagaso.github.io/publications/</guid><description>publication page published Nagaso M. Study of ultrasound wave propagation in a heterogeneous fluid medium for the monitoring of an operating sodium-based nuclear reactor (Doctoral dissertation, Université d&amp;rsquo;Aix Marseille).
Nagaso M, Komatitsch D, Moysan J, Lhuillier C. Numerical simulation of ultrasonic wave propagation in a sodium cooling system in an inhomogeneous temperature field using the spectral-element method. In19th World Conference on Non-Destructive Testing 2016 Jun 13.
Nagaso M, Komatitsch D, Moysan J, Lhuillier C.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mnagaso.github.io/projects/</guid><description>My former and current projects ESFAST : Eikonal-based Solver For Adjoint-State travel-time Tomography I am currently working on this project. Eikonal-based solver for calculating travel times is computationally much lighter than full-waveform inversion. By using this method, we will try to achieve a tomographic image of the Earth structure with a very high resolution. The aim of this project is to develop a numerical library for making the calculation of adjoint-state travel-time tomography, but not only the solver, which is well optimized for the use on HPCs of Exascale-era.</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://mnagaso.github.io/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mnagaso.github.io/resume/</guid><description>Personal date Name: Masaru NAGASO
Address: Singapore
github, gitlab, linkedin, researchgate
Language English (fluent) French (intermediate) Japanese (native) Experience 03.jan.2022 - Present Research fellow Mathematical Imaging and Geophysics Group, Nanyang Technological University, Singapore Lead developer of the project ESFAST (HPC ready eikonal solver and pre/post-processing tools for adjoint-state travel-time tomography).
01.june.2019&amp;ndash;31.dec.2021 Postdoctral research assistant
CNRS-LMA, Marseille, France
Co-lead developer of SPECFEM3D for ChEESE project, which is the international project in the domain of geoscience for preparing Exascale HPC founded from the European Union&amp;rsquo;s Horizon 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>